Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing That
surely someday we just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
A brat who turned into a dragon?
I mean, the boy
How did you know about that, young lady?
Well, to tell the truth,
I saw it all happen.
But I decided not to
tell anybody about it,
because we weren't
supposed to be in there.
We came here on the same boat.
When I saw him change, it scared me.
I'm worried about him.
Oh, I see.
There's no need for you to worry.
He's fine.
This laboratory is big,
and it's got lots of treatment
rooms scattered throughout it.
He's just being kept in a different
part of the lab, that's all.
Oh, really?
Do you know if he's had something to eat?
I don't know why but he
wouldn't even touch his food,
yeah, we got him to start eating again.
Don't you worry about him;
he's doing just fine now.
Listen, whatever you do,
don't tell anyone about the
boy of the secret room—not
even the other kids—it'll
be our little secret,
okay.
Hey, what's
the big idea, bird lady?
How do you like my 10 layer igloo?
Quite a bit thicker than the
last one, isn't it? You see,
it's much harder to break through the snow
walls when they're layered
on top of one another.
You're just trying to
buy time, aren't you?
This thing can't hold me—you're right.
In fact, you could probably break through
all the snow walls in a matter of seconds.
If you agree, then why even father?
There's no way that I'm losing to you.
That's a good point.
Struggle as I may; I have no chance
of ever beating you. However,
sometimes it's the smartest,
not the strongest, who wins the fight.
You can't push
me
away now
that I've got you in my embrace.
You no longer have the
strength to break free.
Slowly but surely, my icy body will drain
your power until there's nothing left.
Eventually, your heart will freeze.
Would you look at that?
It's snowing heavily all around you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Now slowly
close your eyes.
close your eyes
There you go.
Just relax.
Shut up!
Through the floor?
What tremendous power he has.
But that tumble is going to land
him in the trash chute which
leads straight to the garbage
dump that's deep underground.
He won't be able to make it up
here again unless he could fly.
He dug his own grave so to speak.
So long?
You've got to listen to me.
You can't eat anymore.
It's bad for you I know it's
hard, but resist the temptation
I need you to believe me.
You've got to be strong.
You're not getting past me, kids.
I'm not going to let you go
back inside the distant room.
You're just eating a little bit.
No, you can't.
Let go, you're hurting me.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to hurt you.
Get out of our way, you monster.
We want our candy.
This won't work.
I can't stop them without hurting them.
Here's our jam!
Get to the biscuit room!
No, stop!
Stay out of there, kids!
Uh-oh.
The effects of the rumble
ball are wearing off!
Now we can eat all the candy!
Hurry!
Let's go back to the biscuit room!
I can't wait to have some!
No!
That stuff's bad for you!
What'll I do?
I'm so weak, I can't move.
Whoa. You okay?
Bobanosuke!
Where are you?
I'm glad you're here.
I can't handle them alone.
You want to tell us
what's going on, buddy?
Caesar Cloud's trying to
turn the four children into
giants because he wants them
all to become vicious soldiers.
And he's doing it by
giving them drugged candy.
You've got to stop the kids before
they can consume any more of it!
The biscuit room's down
the hall to the left.
That's where they get the candy.
There's a girl named Mocha
who's been helping me.
She's the only child
who's in their right mind.
We've been working together to keep the
others from getting back in the room,
but now she's in danger.
She's been protecting the
candy, and she's all by herself!
We made it!
Candy!
We gotta help, Mocha!
Mil-flu, gigantesco model!
Get out of the way!
I'm afraid I can't hold
them off much longer.
They sure are determined to
get their hands on that stuff!
Mocha!
Give us candy!
You can't have any, can't you
see it's bad for you? Candy! Yay!
I'm telling you guys this
is what's making us sick!
Yeah, Dad!
Look what did they do!
We asked Chopper and his friends to
help us get out of this place, remember?
It's mine! Give it!
No, you gotta listen to them
or we'll never get back home!
It's no use, they're too strong!
Let go and run!
No, no, I can't!
Chase her!
Hey, I'll tell you pretty things
we've got to be in the mouth, Dad!
What?
Yes, it's blocked.
You don't have to worry
about a thing, Mocha, dear.
It's Monet!
Wait, who the hell is she? Ah! It's her!
She's the crazy bird woman
I told you guys about!
Mocha, you shouldn't hog all of the candy.
Be a nice girl and share
it with the others, okay?
Dammit, Vroom!
Now my heart, come back to me!
Here's the counter-shock!
I have a message from Joker.
He said that it's a shame.
My attack didn't work.
I knew exactly how to get
my heart back from Caesar.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I should have guessed you were his lackey.
Don't you have better things to do?
Well, Fargo? Mr. Fargo!
I'm kinda in the middle of something.
Does it have to be now?
Vice Admiral Smoker.
Whatever.
Been mean to kill you.
Might as well get it over with.
Go ahead and try.
The sooner, the better.
I can only look at trash for so long.
before I have to take it out.
Especially filthy pirates like you.
What are those?
They look mighty ominous.
They are, but that's not your business.
There you go.
I don't want the rank and file to
know the truth about you. Got it?
These men, they look up
to you like a father.
If they find out that you're
a traitor, they'll be crushed.
Well, too late now.
They know it all.
I saw them moments ago.
What did you do to them? You'll see.
Vergo!
It looks like I hit a nerve.
Why are you getting so worked up, Smoker?
Don't tell me you're actually concerned
about the welfare of those Navy misfits.
I am a base commander.
I can do what I want to my
good-for-nothing subordinates.
It's a shame it had to end this way,
but now that you know my secret,
I must kill you.
I don't even care if you
are their base commander.
Cause once a unit leaves the base.
It's their commander who's
responsible for keeping them alive.
I'm warning you.
Don't ever lay a hand on my men.
No way! What happened?
There's no place to step!
The whole place is burning
up! What now? Let's hurry!
Grab the injured and run!
Okay, come on, men!
We've got to protect Toshiki!
What do you think you're doing?
Don't agree with it!
He's our foe! What?
That's total crap!
Pirates are free to love who they want!
I gotta admit, Blackleg, You look so
cool fighting fake Vergo back there.
Then watching you blast him like
that made my heart skip a beat.
Yeah, that was pretty sexy if you ask me.
Hey, shut your traps.
You're not really helping
me out here, you know.
Stop acting like he's your friend.
Don't forget he's a pirate.
Whoa, the tank just exploded.
And it smoked fire.
Crap, not good.
It busted a hole in the wall.
Damn, another explosion.
What the hell is going on? Come on! Hurry!
What's the matter?
See that purple stuff?
It's the poisonous gas from outside!
Start running if you want to live!
The gas is traveling fast!
It won't be long before the
whole building is filled!
Get off!
Dumbass!
Go!
Keep running, Tashigi!
You can't stop to think or you'll die!
Get out of here as fast as possible!
Move! Blackleg! Let's go, men!
Pick up the pace or
you're not gonna make it!
I didn't have to lift a finger.
And look, those fools brought
land of the dead inside for me.
But it's too soon.
My life demonstration is not done yet.
You, listen up!
Close the gates to C and
D! Yes, sir. What about R?
Keep that one open.
Can't have them getting lost, so we'll
lure them to the building's first floor.
They're looking for gate R-66, and
the layout of this lab is confusing.
We wouldn't want them going the wrong way.
So we'll just have to guide them there.
Curses.
I loathe this stupid secret room.
Too bad, right?
But once we're done, I'll be free and
I'll never have to come here again
The Straw Hats have
overstayed their welcome.
I'd say it's time for them
to be properly punished
I've got Joker on my side,
and now I have the opportunity
to kill all of them
in the ideal manner Master
we're awaiting orders.
We're ready for combat Yes,
but may I ask why you've summoned
us here to Vega punks former
command room Wasn't he responsible
for the accident four years ago?
We've got a score to settle with him, too.
Let's get him.
Why are we wasting time standing
around here staring at each other?
I mean, should we be fighting?
No, not yet.
You gentlemen are my backup plan.
You're the best soldiers I have,
so I cannot risk losing you.
Oh, Master.
Now, allow me to explain
the plan to all of you.
As I said before, once the gates
to C and D have been closed,
the only open routes
through the laboratory
will lead to the first
floor of building R,
which is directly beneath us.
The Straw Hats, G5, the children,
it doesn't matter whether
they're friend or foe,
all of the survivors in the lab
will be forced into that room.
The first floor has external vents
which can bring in outside air.
In other words, we'll be able to
fill the room with land of the dead.
There'll be no way for them to escape!
They'll be stuck breathing that air!
It'll be like a giant gas chamber!
And soon, they will all die!
The best part is we'll be
broadcasting it so my shadow
brokers in the new world
can witness the slaughter.
Then they'll respect me!
They'll know my greatness!
I hate to ask this, but Master Caesar,
I don't mean to doubt you or anything,
sir, but did you create
the deadly poison gas?
Forgive me, Master.
It seems a lot like Vegapunk's gas,
the one from the accident four
years ago, and thing is, Master,
it freaks us out.
Just allow me to explain everything!
Please, men!
That day!
It still haunts me!
Oh, how I tried to stop the mad scientist!
No!
What if this dangerous
weapon exploded, I cried!
Just think of all the innocent
people who would be killed!
Please, Vegapunk, don't do this!
But there was no stopping him.
and now he's the head of the
navy science division and
he's widely considered the
world's greatest scientist.
It's not fair.
It should have been me.
I cannot accept it.
How could someone so heartless come
to be praised as the best of all?
Tell me after what he's
done—does he still?
still I'll deserve to
be called the greatest!
That's why I must prove him wrong!
I don't want to create
a weapon of mass murder,
but I'm afraid it must be
done in order to prove I am.
the greatest scientist in the world!
Please, trust me!
Once the navy realizes that I
deserve to be their lead scientist.
Then I'll be fulfilled and I shall use
my knowledge to bring peace and unity.
Master, forgive me, master you're
right; how could I doubt you?
I'm sorry, me too.
You are the god of salvation.
Don't do it, Caesar.
Stop it!
I'm warning you.
Shut it down!
You're putting everyone
on the island in danger.
You realize if that weapon explodes,
innocent life will be lost.
Shut up!
Ignorant fool—this is a
military testing site.
This is my job.
Back off!
As you may know, the navy wants to kill
as many pirates as they possibly can.
I'm simply creating a new weapon
for them, designed to do just that.
It's dangerous.
I'm sure your weapon will kill pirates,
but you know what else it'll
do—kill a bunch of civilians, idiot!
See that's something
called collateral damage.
If they don't evacuate,
they deserve what's coming.
Wipe them all out, and we'll
finally have world peace.
How could
you say that, Caesar?
You're so what you think?
I'm cruel perhaps, but so are you?
are you Think about it.
You're using the prisoners
as your guinea pigs.
Let's be honest.
Is there really a difference between them?
I think not.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku may be soft, but
Admiral Aka-Inu, on the other hand,
I bet he would love one of my weapons.
Now, scram!
I don't need you interrupting my work.
Vegapunk's just jealous,
and I can't blame him.
I am a genius.
Besides, his silly human enlargement
experiment is nothing but a failure.
You need to be a real magician to make the
human body grow that much
in such a short time.
I tried to tell him what to do.
What he needs is children.
Those who are growing.
And fill them with drugs.
I believe that's the only way.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't try to fight us.
I'm almost finished making a weapon
so powerful it's beyond comprehension.
Vegapunk, I demand to
know the meaning of this.
You've been terminated from
the science division, Caesar.
You've gone too far this time.
I can't cover for you anymore.
You gotta be killing me.
No, don't do it, Caesar.
Closing the gate between C and B.
The gate between D and B is now closed.
That's it.
The passageways between buildings B,
C, and D have been secured, Master.
Come on, run like hell, you guys!
Hold on, you can talk!
Who the hell are you?
I, uh...
Who am I?
I am the one who should
be asking that of you!